{
  "list": [
    {
      "question": "What has many holes, but holds lots of water?",
        "choices": [
          "An umbrella",
          "A bucket",
          "A sponge",
          "A slice of bread"
        ],
      "answer": "A sponge"
    },
    {
      "question": "What goes up when the rain comes down?",
      "choices": [
        "The temperature",
        "Umbrellas",
        "Depression",
        "Car accidents"
      ],
      "answer": "Umbrellas"
    },
    {
      "question": "I'm not clothes, but I cover your body. The more im used, the thinner I grow",
      "choices": [
        "Hair",
        "Skin",
        "Bar of Soap",
        "Cologne"
      ],
      "answer": "Bar of Soap"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have a head and a tail, but no body. What am I?",
      "choices": [
        "A lizard",
        "Dollar bills",
        "I hate riddles",
        "A Coin"
      ],
      "answer": "A Coin"
    },
    {
      "question": "I'm black from a bag, Red when you use me, White when you're done with me. What am I?",
      "choices": [
        "Charcoal",
        "Televisions",
        "Alcohol",
        "Clothes"
      ],
      "answer": "Charcoal"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the beginning of end and the end of universe?",
      "choices": [
        "The meaning of life",
        "The letter E",
        "Time",
        "Space makes my head hurt"
      ],
      "answer": "The letter E"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have keys but no locks, I have a space but no room, You can enter, but can't go outside. What am I?",
      "choices": [
        "A Prison",
        "A Bank",
        "A Keyboard",
        "A Zoo"
      ],
      "answer": "A Keyboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "They are Dark, and always on the run. Without the sun, there would be none.",
      "choices": [
        "Shadows",
        "Life",
        "Solar Panels",
        "Rain Forest"
      ],
      "answer": "Shadows"
    },
    {
      "question": "What lives as long as it eats but dies when it drinks?",
      "choices": [
        "Humans",
        "Rivers",
        "Fire",
        "The American political process"
      ],
      "answer": "Fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is this game over?",
      "choices": [
        "No",
        "No",
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "answer": "Yes"
    }
  ]
}